I am an engineering student, with an interest in content creation and writing. I am a passionate and persuasive writer, speaker and orator. I believe in the immense power words hold and aim to be a detrimental tool in enhancing this experience for organizations I work for. I also identify myself as a quick learner and am determined to expand my skill set in the best possible way.

CONTACT

- ambx.work@gmail.com
- +91 8136982845
- www.hibafathima.com
- m www.linkedin.com/in/ambx
- Mangalore 575001
 Karnataka, India

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENG.

2018-Present

CGPA: 7.9/10.0

Sahyadri College of Engineering and Management, Mangaluru

SKILLS

Literary

Formally trained in British and American English, formal writing, blog-writing, creativewriting, copywriting

Programming

C, JS, HTML/CSS, Python

Others

GSuite, MS Office, Adobe Ai/Xd, Git/GitHub, Figma

HIBA FATHIMA

WORK EXPERIENCE

B2B SAAS CONTENT WRITER | CONTENSIFY

Full-time | Aug 2021 - Present | www.contensifyhq.com

- Plan, research and write blog posts on a weekly basis for various B2B SaaS companies
- Plan and prepare content calendars for social media (Instagram and LinkedIn) engagement posts

E-COMMERCE STORE CO-FOUNDER | SOBER TWENTIES & CO.

Full-time | Oct 2021 - Present | <u>www.sober20s.com</u>

• Ideate, plan, and execute all managerial, design, production, marketing, and customer support tasks.

B2B SAAS CONTENT WRITER | DRESMA.AI

Freelance | Apr 2022 - Present | www.dresma.ai

 Prepare SEO-rich blogs on a weekly basis to help improve organic traffic for e-commerce centric products

CONTENT WRITER | GOODERA

Internship | Jan 2022 - Mar 2022 | www.goodera.com

- Researched and wrote topical, thought leadership and listicle blog posts to boost visibility of nonprofit partners
- Curated educational and topical social media content

CONTENT WRITER | FIRST MAIN BANGALORE

Internship | Dec 2020 - Feb 2021 | www.firstmain.org

- Planned and prepared content for social media (Instagram and LinkedIn) engagement posts
- Researched topics and wrote blog posts on a weekly basis
- Helped manage content for the official website, flyers

TECHNICAL CONTENT WRITER | DSI MANGALORE

 $Part\text{-}time \mid 2019 \mid \underline{www.dreamsoftin.com}$

- Helped curate and structure content for the official website
- Prepared product reports regularly for detailed analysis

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Sahyadri Open Source Women's Community

Community Lead | 2020-Present

TEDxSCEM

Head of Content | 2019

Sahyadri Toastmasters

President | 2019-2020 VP-PR | 2020

Django Girls Mangaluru Chapter

Community Lead | 2020-Present

U&I India

Volunteer | 2019-Present